Guide to the History of Education Society collection, 1960-2013 MS2341
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Governance and Society records, 1960-2006; Series 2
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Labaree, Tyack, Wise, Sennett, 1983-1984; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Milton Canter, 1982; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Mr. Davison, Vaughn E. Davison & Ms. Mackin, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson & Mr. Ross, Mattingly, March, 1982; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Ms. Hookaway, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Ms. Verbrugge, 1982; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Ms. Wells, 1981; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, Paul H. Mattingly, and Professor Stone, Eisenstein, Harvey, Charlton, Degler, Jim, 1980-1981; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Peter G. Pollack, December 14, 1979; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 81)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Peter G. Pollack w/ attachment, 1979-1980; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 82)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Akenson, March 30, 1984; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Albisetti, October 29, 1981; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 84)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Anderson, February, 1982; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Berlin, May 6, 1982; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Beyerchen, December 18, 1980; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 87)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Biebel, 1983-1984; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 88)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Breitenbach, May 25, 1985; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Breitenbach, April 30, 1985; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 90)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Brewer & McClelland, 1979; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 91)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Brown, Ryan, and Cantor, 1982-1984; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 92)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Burney, May 8, 1984; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 93)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Burney, April 24, 1984; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 94)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Carper, 1981; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 95)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, and Professor Carper, Mattingly, 1978-1979; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 96)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Chase, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 97)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Conway, 1980; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 98)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Cutler, April, 1984; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 99)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Davey, 1985; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Day, December 16, 1981; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 101)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Engel, October 14, 1980; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 102)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Engel, March 3, 1981; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 103)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Ettling, Ellen, Boben, Mr. Mclachlan, Karl, 1983-1985; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 104)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Fleming, 1979; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 105)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Frank, October 19, 1981; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 106)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Friedman, Spence, Barnet, Woodside, Keenan, Li, Cohen, Naquin, 1979-1985; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 107)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Friedriche, March 8, 1981; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 108)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Gagnon, 1979; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 109)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Giles, March 22, 1984; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 110)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Graham, Rodgers, 1985; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 111)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Greven, May 31, 1984; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 112)
  - Correspondence with Carl Kaestle, 1980-1981; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence between the Nominating Committee of the History of Education Society, 1976-1977; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and V.W. Leonard, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and William E. Fuller, October, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence with Peter C. Holloran, May 30, 1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence between Prize Committee, History of Education, and Carl Kaestle, December 10, 1980; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence between President, Directors, Members of History of Education Society and Ronald D. Cohen, October 15, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence between Prize Committee of History of Education Society and Carl Kaestle, December 10, 1980; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence between Professor Carl Kaestle and Wayne J. Urban, 1980; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence between Professor Chipman and Paul H. Mattingly, 1978; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence between Professor Christopher Lucas and George L. Newsome, November 16, 1977; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence between Professor Clarence J. Karier and Alison, 1977; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence between Professor Clarence J. Karier and History of Education Society Board of Members, 1977-1978; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence between Professor Don Matin and Sol Cohen, October 20, 1980; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence between Professor Donald Warren and Wayne Urban, January 16, 1980; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence between Professor Edward McClellan, Geraldine F. Clifford, and William Eaton, April 13, 1977; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence between Professor H.J. Hanham and Paul Mattingly, 1971, 1973; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence between Professor Harry K. Carson and Wayne J. Urban, February 4, 1980; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence between Professor Joan N. Burtsyn, Professor David Tyack, Professor J. Donald Wilson, 1980-1981; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence between Professor Jurgen Herbst and Clarence J. Karier, October 24, 1977; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence between Professor Maris Vinosuskis, Professor David Mater, Professor Frederick M. Binder & Robert K. Sherman, 1980; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence between Professor Noah K. Dzobo and Paul Mattingly, 1974; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence between Professor Sol Cohen & Wayne J. Urban, August 1, 1980; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence between Professor Urban and Members of the Board, July, 1980; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence between Professor Urban, Wagner, Finklestein, Herbst, Mattingly, Sherewshewsky, Ms. Nancy Clay, and Peter A. Sola, January 9, 1979; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence between Professor Urban and Professor M. Heineman, 1980; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence between Professor Ureh, Paul H. Mattingly, and Bill, 1978; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence between R. Johnson and Paul H. Mattingly, 1978; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence between Richard J. Altenbaugh and Jurgen Herbst, September 14. 1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence between Richard J. Altenbaugh and Paul Mattingly, September 24, 1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence between Richard J. Altenbaugh and Sol Cohen, August 24, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence between Richard Klayman and Paul H. Mattingly, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence between Robert Church, Joseph Kett, Marvin Lazerson, Kathryn Moore, and Carl Kaestle, September 9, 1981; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence between Robert Fancher and Executive Officers, December 12, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence between Robert H. Beck and Editor, February 27, 1985; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence between Robert Hutchins and Paul Mattingly, March 7, 1977; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence between Robert J. Havighburst, Carol S. Gruber, and Paul Mattingly, 1978-1979; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence between Robert N. Kingdon and Robin Berson, October 1, 1980; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence between Robert McCaul and Henry Perleinson, 1966; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence between Robert McClintock and Paul, March 21, 1979; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence between Robert Newton Barger and Paul H. Mattingly, December 16, 1977; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence between Robert Westbrook and Paul H. Mattingly, 1978-1979; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence between Robert Westbrook and Robin, April 13, 1983; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, A.V. Yannicppoulos, and Richard J. Wolff, 1984-1985; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Arthur Engel, February 12, 1985; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, Arthur Engel, Robert W. Zuber, Thomas Laqueur, and Sheldon Rothblatt, 1984-1985; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Auvo Kostiainen, 1979-1980; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Barbara Brenzel, March, 1979; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Barbara Finkelstein, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Barry Keenan, September 4, 1979; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Brian W. Taylor, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, Bruce A. Kimball, J. Stephen Haslett, and Paul H. Mattingly, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Charle Biebel, August 30, 1979; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Charles Burgess, April, 1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Charles M. Pye, June 12, 1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Charles R. Wilson, May, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Christopher Eisele, 1983-1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, Christopher J. Lucas, and Suzanne W. Barnett, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Clint Warmath, 1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and David, 1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, David Adams, and Frederick Stefon, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and David B. Mock, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and David Carson, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and David Hogan, September 4, 1979; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, David Marr, and Gail P. Kelly, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and David Tyack, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Dean Griffiths, June 23, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Di Bona, 1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Dr. Abbott, Professor Houston, Davey Berger, 1983-1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Dr. Bishop, 1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Dr. Catarsi, 1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Dr. D'Souza, 1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Dr. Mangan, May 22, 1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Dr. Warren, 1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Edward Berman, 1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Edward R. Beauchamp, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Eileen M. Eagan, 1985; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Eileen S. Hammer, 1983-1985; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 78)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, Elizabeth Swing, and Allan Horlock, 1975, 1979-1981; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 79)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Erik Hansen, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and F. Raymond McKenna, 1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 81)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Gary B. Bullert, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 82)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Gentlepeople, December 16, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Gentlepeople, June 1, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 84)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Gentlepeople, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Gentlepeople, October 19, 1981; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Gentlepeople, February 26, 1985; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 87)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, Harvey J. Graff, and William Eaton, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 88)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Harvey Strum, 1982-1983; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Harvey Strum, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 90)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Herbert Gutman, November 16, 1978; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 91)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Huub Wijler, September 10, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 92)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and J.A. Smith, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 93)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and J.R. Roberts, September 16, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 94)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and J.B. Thomas and Ian Davey, 1983; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 95)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, J. Stephen Hazlett and Carol Englehardt, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 96)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Jack C. Lane, 1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 97)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Jack C. Lane, April 10, 1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 98)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Jame L. Leloudis, 1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 99)
  - Correspondence between Robin B., James S., Richard D., and Paul M., 1978-1979; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, John Sommerville, and Janice Gordon Richter, 1984-1985; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 101)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Joel Spring, 1983; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 102)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, Joseph Kett, and Christine M. Shea, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 103)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, and Jurgen Herbst, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 104)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Katherine Kennedy, 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 105)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Kozo Kosaka, 1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 106)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Lawrence O. Christensen, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 107)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Levi Elwell, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Luis M. Lazaro Lorente, 1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and M. Chartier, 1978; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Margaret A. Laughlin, 1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Margaret F. Maxwell, 1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Marie Cleary, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Marilee Charbonneau, March, 1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Maurice Hogden, October 7, 1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Maurice Wolfthal, 1982-1983; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence between Robin B., Marvin L., Harold W., and Roser L., 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, Marvin Lazerson, and Sheila Slaughter, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, Marvin Lazerson, Toby S. Tetenbaum, and Thomas A. Mulkeen, 1984-1985; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Max Okenfuss, April 10, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Michael Carey, 1983-1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Mr. Clamp, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Mr. Erickson, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Mr. Erickson, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Mr. Hardman, 1983-1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Mr. La Volpa, 1983; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Mr. O'Brien, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Ms. Caswell, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Ms. Schiller, October 2, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Huseman, 1983-1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and P. Butterfield, 1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, Patrick J. Harrigan, and Judith Wishnia, 1984-1985; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Patricia T. Brooke, 1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Paul W. McBride, February, 1979; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Paul Vogt, 1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Peter H. Hare, 1983; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Phillip Greven, September 4, 1979; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Phillip McCann, September 4, 1979; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence between Phillip Reed Rulon & Wayne J. Urban, 1980; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Abbott, January 12, 1983; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Anderson, February, 1980; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Armstrong, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Bartholomew, November 17, 1983; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Bartholomew, May, 1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Berard, 1980-1983; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Beales, Murphy, Kuklick, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Berson, May 15, 1981; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Boucouvalas, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Burstyn, January, 1983; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Clements, November 24, 1981; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor David and Professor Johnson, 1980-1981; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Finkelstein, November 13, 1980; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Gaffield, 1983; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Gilmore, 1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence between Robin and Professor Gershman, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Gilbert, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Greene, 1981; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Griswold, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Grubbs, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Gullickson, Scott, Gelbart, 1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Gutman, October 5, 1981; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Hall, December 6, 1983; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Herbst, May 18, 1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Harlan, Hornsby, 1979; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Hornsby, December 18, 1960; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Hornsby, November 13, 1980; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Hornsby, January, 1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Horton, 1980, 1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Houston, November 25, 1980; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Lamba, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor McDonald, Houston, 1980-1981; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professors Imber & Kett, 1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Karl, Skowronek, 1982-1983; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Katz, March 8, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Lane, September 18, 1980; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Laqueur, April 29, 1981; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Lazerson, February 23, 1981; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Lynn, October 1, 1980; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor McLeod, Jones, Sanderson, Engel, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Morantz and Friedlander, 1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Maxley, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 74)